<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 01:22:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Redis with Spring Boot</title>
      <link>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/using-redis-with-spring-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 01:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/using-redis-with-spring-boot/</guid>
      <description>Redis is an open source, in-memory data structure store, used as a database, cache and message broker. Here we would use Redis as Message Broker to create messaging layer in our demo finance application. This application consist of multiple micro services which interact with each other. We would create event driven construct, where services would connect to messaging layer and would publish and subscribe events to messaging layer. Auto reloading feature does not work out of the box in Intellij.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Boot Devtools on Intellij</title>
      <link>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/spring-boot-devtools-on-intellij/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 01:11:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/spring-boot-devtools-on-intellij/</guid>
      <description>Auto reloading feature does not work out of the box in Intellij. Below are the changes required to make it work correctly.
Spring Boot provide niche feature of hot reloading for a Spring Boot application.
It recompile your java application as soon as you make a change. But most important aspect is that it only recompile only those files in which changes are made. Thus process take quite a short time compared to complete application build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create your own blog website using Hugo in less than 1 hour for free</title>
      <link>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/create-your-own-blog-website-using-hugo-in-less-than-1-hour-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 01:22:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bhanuchaddha.github.io/create-your-own-blog-website-using-hugo-in-less-than-1-hour-for-free/</guid>
      <description>In the technical age, publishing articles online is a great way to express yourself. It can be of any form like tutorial, blogs, reviews, editorials and much more.
It is almost defacto to use Medium for blogging now a days. It provides many benefits like :
 Focus only on content. Formatting is handled by Medium platform SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to promote the article in google search Easy interface to write article in browser itself And many more like support for images, videos and code reference using Gist  Then Why should you have your own blog?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>